Guide to the Bryan Gallery of Christian Art Print Collection circa 1525-circa 1870 PR 143
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Prints, before 1528-1817, undated
  - [148] [Small heads of French kings], undated (Folder 12)
  - [149] [Mary and Jesus] by Batreri, undated (Folder 12)
  - [150] [Holy Family with cherubs], undated (Folder 15)
  - [151] [People on clouds, in Heaven] after Michelangelo (1475-1564), undated (Folder 15)
  - [152] [Mother with son—Cupid?] after Bernardino Nocchi (1741-1812), by Pietro Fontana (1762-1837), undated (Folder 15)
  - [153] "St. Thomas Wharton," after Anthony van Dyck (1599-1641), drawn by Josiah Boydell (1752-1817), engraved by Valentine Green (1739-1813), 1775 (Folder 15)
  - [154] "La Sacra Famiglia," after Guercino (1591-1666), by Francesca Rosaspina (1762-1841), undated (Folder 15)
  - [155] [Holy Family on pedestal] after Peter Paul Rubens (1577-1640), drawn by Abraham Jansz van Diepenbeeck (1596-1675), engraved by Hendrick Snyers, undated (Folder 15)
  - [156] [Lucifer fighting Archangel Michael] after Peter Paul Rubens (1577-1640), by Jonas Suyderhoef (circa 1613-1686), 1642 (Folder 15)
  - [157] "Les Disciples d'Emaus," after Paolo Veronese (1528-1588), by Simon Thomassin (1655-1733), undated (Folder 15)
  - [158] "Carolus de Longueual," after Peter Paul Rubens (1577-1640), by Lucas Emil Vorsterman (1595-1675), undated (Folder 15)
- Series II. Photographs, undated
  - [159] Photographs of the Alhambra [7 albumen prints, 8 x 10 inches], undated (Folder 19)
  - [160] Photographs of paintings in Perugia [23 albumen prints, 5 x 7 inches and smaller], undated (Folder 20)
- Series III. Other items, undated
  - [161] [Christ being taken from cross] Michelangelo Merisi da Caravaggio (1573-1610) [photomechanical reproduction], undated (Folder 12)
  - [162] "The Birth of the Savior," printed by George Baxter (1804-1867) [photomechanical reproduction], undated (Folder 12)
  - [163?] Amateur drawing of a priest, undated (Folder 12)
  - [Unnumbered] [Satyrs?], [1774?] (Folder 12)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Although found with the Bryan Gallery of Christian Art Print Collection, it is unclear if this item (marked in pencil with the accession number 1858.92.043) is part of the whole.